toppersworld.com 2017-09-25

# Privacy Policy

At Toppersworld.com, we give utmost importance to the privacy of our visitors.  This privacy policy will outline the type of personal information that we collect from our visitors who visit Toppersworld.com.  
**Log Files**  
Our website, Toppersworld.com like many other website uses log file to store information about the visitor.  The log file information includes Internet Service Provider (ISP), internet protocol (IP) addresses , number of clicks to analyze trends, type of browser used, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, trace user’s movement within the site, and demographic information.  The IP addresses and other information that we store at not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Toppersworld.com  does use cookies to store information about record user-specific information, visitors preferences on which pages the user visit or access, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Toppersworld.com .  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Toppersworld.com  and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
**Google Adsense**  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Toppersworld.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
Toppersworld.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Toppersworld.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Image And External Content**

ToppersWorld.com does not claim credit for any images featured on our website unless otherwise noted.  All the visual contents displayed above are copyrighted to their respectful owners.  We make all efforts to link back to the original source wherever possible.  If you own rights to any of the pictures/images displayed on our website and does not want them to be displayed on our website, then you can contact us through the Email-ID mentioned below and your image/images will be promptly removed.

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Kumar Radhakrishnan  
admin@toppersworld.com
